在这里  我们将做一个名为Sunshine的天气应用
In the course, we're going to build a weather app called Sunshine. The main
主界面是本周天气预报列表  特别强调呈现了今天的
screen is a list of this week's forecast, with an emphasized presentation for
天气情况  只需要看一眼  我就能决定
today's weather. With just a quick glance, I can decide if,
今天的编码地点  到底该在家  还是应该去公园
today is a stay inside, in code day. Or if I should code from the park,
我们有一个天气情况的图标  比如下雪
instead. We have icons to indicate conditions, like snow,
下雨  有雾或者晴天  我们可以滑动这个列表
rain, fog or sunshine. We can scroll through the list,
查看更久的天气预报  当我们点击某个天气预报情况时
to see a long range forecast. With a click on one of the forecasts,
将会打开到一个有更详细天气信息的视图
will bring up a detailed view containing the rest of the weathery goodness,
我们还可以在此视图上将天气情况分享给我们的朋友
which also gives us the ability to share the weather with our friends.
我们可以点击Setting设置计量温度单位和地点
We can go to Settings and change the unit of measure, as well as the location.
这个应用同样可以发送系统通知  以便于我们不打开应用
The app can even post system wide notifications, to let us know about weather
也能看到天气信息  可能你会问  我们为何
conditions without even entering the app. So, you might ask, why are we
要做一个天气应用呢  我们选择它是因为它比较简单
building a weather app? We chose the weather app because it's a simple concept,
涉及到了大量我们要教给大家的核心API  同时每个人都需要查看天气
which touches most of the core APIs we want to teach and everyone can relate to
除非你在地下室住  在本课的结束  你将能够使用
weather, unless you're in a bunker. By the end of the course, you'll be able
这些API来构建你的最终项目应用啦
to use those APIs and concepts to build your own app for your final project.